[{"answer": "To be honest, it's hard to tell.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What is the reaction of the Afghani people to this announcement by the president?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "You make a good point there, Piers.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "I mean aren't the Taliban just waiting in the mountains for the American troops to pull out and just to get back to what they did before?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, not really.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Or hasn't it really been a counterterrorist operation that will now continue with more emphasis on Afghan troops than American troops?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "No, they really haven't.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Have they?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "But he didn't do it.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "So isn't he entitled to remind the American people that it was a pretty successful mission, that it got rid of a pretty awful man?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's very important.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "What is the historical significance of the president's visit to Afghanistan tonight and the speech he's made outlining the future there?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "No, he didn't get into, you know, a lot of politic -- political talk if you will in this 10-minute address he gave to the nation from the Bagram Air Base.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "No, it's cheap politics.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Let me turn to you, Doug Brinkley, I mean is that a fair criticism of the president, do you think, that he's just -- really this is just cheap politics?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, that was over the top.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What was your reaction to that quote there from the Senate Armed Services Committee member?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "That's yet to be determined.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Has America really got more out of this whole conflict in Afghanistan than the Soviets did?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I am, I am personally impressed.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "When you look at President Obama's foreign policies since he became president, are you impressed by the way that he has conducted it?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, it's also a reminder in the great sweep of history that it's very hard to judge presidential decisions, presidential administrations at the time.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "But isn't it just weird that in the modern political world with the rhetoric as it is that he can't even get credit for something so straightforward?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, he certainly has a fight on his hands.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "He's got a fight on his hands, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "I would say covering Dr. Martin Luther King in the Civil Rights Movement, which was my first big assignment for CBS News.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "When you look back at it, when you finished the book and shut the page, which of all the stories was the one that had the most personal connection for you?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I get angry.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "ATHER: Well, my personal opinion is we have not fully recovered.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Will it ever properly recover from that day?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I don't in this regard -- again, my personal opinion -- I think the sort of taking the emphasis off Iraq after the initial success and placing it on Afghanistan.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Do you think American responded the right way?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, we don't have the great benefit of hindsight.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "When you look back on the whole thing, knowing everything you now know, is there anything you would have done differently, with the great benefit of hindsight?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Do you believe to this day those documents were genuine?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Have you ever had any conversation with President Bush since that?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Dwight Eisenhower would probably be my choice.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Who was the one if you could choose one guy to lead your country?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Not only did I not imagine it, we used to sit around in the shank of the evening over an adult beverage talking about civil rights.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "When you covered the Civil Rights Movement, did you ever imagine in your lifetime there would be a black president?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "That wasn't a question.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "May I answer that?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Frankly, I don't think any reporter could do it today.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Be that inquisitive, that interrogatory?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, American journalism is in crisis, in my opinion.", "docId": "120501pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "When you take an overview, what do you think of modern journalism standards?", "qSentId": 493}]